

POPICA ANDREI

Data entry | Marketing Assistant - Zenda Outlet

Age 25 from Bucuresti, not married

Contact details

Email: andrei.popica@yahoo.com Tel: +40767453557

Address: sector 3

About me

I'm an objective person who like to think logical or to see the logical in things. The 8 years of real-profile studies (High school Mathematics-Informatics and Faculty of Constructions) helped me develop an analyte thinking. On professional side so far, i have activated in areas where i put in practice the knowledge accumulated and have acquired some new ones.

Other passions: psychology, which helps me a lot in interacting with other people.

Professional experience

Experience by Construction / Facilities : 4 months

departments Engineering : 10 months

Administrative / Logistics: 1 year and 11 months

Marketing: 9 months

Jan 2019 - present

Data entry | Marketing Assistant - Zenda Outlet

10 months Bucharest | Marketing | Commerce / Retail

I take care of the marketing part (Helping the Specialist), doing the following things:-Facebook Ads, admimistrating the Instagram page, Keeping track of spending and budgets. I take care of everything that means product that appears on the site (prices, categories, etc).

Also, on the graphics side i make the banners that the site needs.

Acquired skills and knowledge:

Microsoft Office, Photoshop, Microsoft Excel

Oct 2017 - Jul 2018

Technical Sketch/Construction engineer - Fdp Pro Cons SRL

Bucharest | Engineering | Construction

Structural design (resistance calculations).

Preparation of execution plans

Net salary: 2000 RON

Jan 2017 - Apr 2017

Technician - Accuro

4 months

10 months

Bucharest | Construction / Facilities | Construction

Acquired skills and knowledge:

AutoCAD

Jan 2015 - Nov 2016

Administrator - Camin Studentes Giulesti

1 year and 11 months Bucharest | Administrative / Logistics | Administrative / Public Sector

During the faculty, I was the manager of this home, dealing with all the problems that occurred in the course of time. These include: Paying bills, managing money, maintaining a pleasant environment, repairing objects.

Education

2014 - 2017 Bachelor's degree - UTCB

FCCIA | Bucuresti

2013 - 2014 Bachelor's degree - UNITBV

FCCIA | Brasov

Skills

General skills

Sociable person, html - beginner, CSS - beginner, python - beginner

Skills from work experience

Microsoft Office, Photoshop, Microsoft Excel, AutoCAD

Foreign languages

English - Medium

Other info

Certifications

CodeBerry Programing School

period Jul 2019 - Sep 2019

Hobbies

Passion for Psychology, Reading, Travels

Driving license

Category B

acquired on 15 Jun 2012